const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Where is user Photos App content stored?',
      answers: [
        'Photos App',
        'Photos Library',
        'Photos Database',
        'Photos Directory'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'Photos Library'
    },
    {
      question:
        'How long does content remain in recentley deleted?',
      answers: [
        '24 hours',
        '90 days',
        '30 days',
        '14 days'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        '30 days'
    },
    {
      question:
        'In addition to Live, how many Live Photo Effects are there?',
      answers: [
        '3',
        '4',
        '2',
        'None'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '3'
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you import to the Photos App?',
      answers: [
        'Drag content to within Photos App window',
        'Drag content to Photos App icon',
        'Go to File > Import, then navigate to location and choose review for import',
        'All of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above'
    },
    {
      question:
        'All except which are ways of sharing from the Photos App?',
      answers: [
        'In menu bar go to Share > ...',
        'Click the Share Button in the toolbar and make choice',
        'In menu bar go to File > Share > ...',
        'In menu bar go to File > Export > ...'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'In menu bar go to Share > ...'
    },
    {
      question: 'Content in the Photos section of Library can be sorted by all of the following except?',
      answers: [
        'Years',
        'Months',
        'Days',
        'Accumulative'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Accumulative'
    },
    {
      question:
        'How do you create a new Media Type in Albums?',
      answers: [
        'Go to File > Create > Media Type',
        'You can\'t. It is based off the type of content present',
        'Upon import, choose which type of Media your importing',
        'Secondary click a Picture or Video and choose "Change Media Type" to create category'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'You can\'t. It is based off the type of content present'
    },
    {
      question: 'If you suddenly have 10,000 duplicate items, what is a likely cause?',
      answers: [
        '"Duplicate Items" was used after having highlighting all',
        'The Photos App has a bug which needs to be fixed',
        'The Pictures System Folder was likely mistakenly imported to the Photos App',
        'A 3rd party App is likely the cause'
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'The Pictures System Folder was likely mistakenly imported to the Photos App'
    },
    {
      question: 'How could you best address an accidental import?',
      answers: [
        'Go to the Imports area, highlight and delete affected import',
        'Download a duplicate cleaning App',
        'Go through all duplicate items and delete each item manually',
        'Live with issue, and get used to seeing double'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Go to the Imports area, highlight and delete affected import'
    },
    {
      question:
        'All of the following are ways to organize content in the Photos App except?',
      answers: [
        'Albums',
        'Smart Albums',
        'Folders',
        'Book'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Book'
    }
  ];